Guide to the UE National Office Records Relating to District 9 and District 9 Locals, 1936-1990s UE.4.1.9
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- District 9 Locals, 2.
  - Local 957
    - Local 957 Outgoing Correspondence, October 17, 1952-May 9, 1955 (Box 7, Folder 83)
      - Kelly to Emspak Regarding Seperate Charter and IUE Inter-union Rivalry, March 7, 1955; 7.
      - Kelly to Emspak Regarding Per Capita, May 9, 1955; 8.
      - Kelly to UE Regarding Cedar Rapids Square D, 9.
    - Local 957 Detroit Correspondence, November 20, 1963-March 21, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 84)
    - Local 957 Leaflets, 1954 (Box 7, Folder 85)
      - "To Square D Workers", September 8, 1954; 1.
      - "An Appeal to the Negro Community", September 12, 1954; 2.
      - "Red Smear Fizzles", December 1, 1954; 3.
      - "UAW-CIO Supports Square D Strike", 1954; 4.
      - "Detroit Is Still a Union Town", 1954; 5.
      - "It's Everybodys Fight", 1954; 6.
    - Local 957 Square D Striker, September 1954 (Box 7, Folder 86)
    - Local 957 Ford Facts, September 11-18, 1954 (Box 7, Folder 87)
    - Local 957 Newspaper Clippings, 1954 (Box 7, Folder 88)
      - "Turmoil Returns to Square D", September 8, 1954; 1.
      - "Council Hits Police Tactics of Square D", September 9, 1954; 2.
      - "Massed Pickets Defy Court Ban", September 9, 1954; 3.
      - "Detroit Mounties Ride at Square D", 1954; 4.
    - Local 957 Charles Kelly Pamphlet, 1955 (Box 7, Folder 89)
    - Local 957 Seperate Charters, October 19-December 5, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 90)
      - John Gojack Telegram to Julius Emspak, October 19, 1950; 1.
      - Emspak to Gojack, October 23, 1950; 2.
      - Gojack to All Square D Members, November 16, 1950; 3.
      - Gojack to Local 937 Shop Committee Members, November 16, 1950; 4.
      - Emspak to Gojack, December 5, 1950; 5-6.
      - Emspak to David Mates, December 5, 1950; 7.
    - Local 957 Strike, July 12-October 19, 1954 (Box 7, Folder 91)
      - David Mates to James Matles, July 12, 1954; 1.
      - Matles to Mates with Charles Kelly Letter to Ernest Moyer, July 13, 1954; 2.
      - Julius Emspak to UE Locals, July 26, 1954; 3.
      - Emspak to Mates, August 13, 1954; 4.
      - Detroit Tool and Die Council Statement, September 8, 1954; 5.
      - John Gojack to All Local Unions, September 9-20, 1954; 6-8.
      - Joseph McCann to Mates, September 30, 1954; 9.
      - Mates to Matles with Strike Contributions and Square D Pledges, September 22, 1954; 10.
      - Mates to Matles with Contribution List, October 19, 1954; 11.
    - Local 957 Cedar Rapids Organization, October 25-December 8, 1954 (Box 7, Folder 92)
      - James Matles to Robert Logsden, October 25, 1954; 1.
      - Logsden to Matles, November 16-20, 1954; 2-3.
      - Matles to David Mates, November 24, 1954; 4.
      - Mates to Logsden, December 8, 1954; 5.
    - Local 957 Magnavox Campaign Expenses, February 23-24, 1955 (Box 7, Folder 93)
      - John Gojack to James Matles, February 23, 1955; 1.
      - Matles to Gojack, February 24, 1955; 2.
    - Local 957 Detroit Westinghouse Electric Corporation, August 1, 1967-December 26, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 94)
    - Local 957 Subsidies and Other Monies, August 10, 1970-September 6, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 95)
    - Local 957 Supplements Rates, November 1, 1950-December 9, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 96)
    - Local 957 Supplements Rates, July 25, 1960-September 29, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 97)
    - Local 957 Correspondence, April 28, 1955 (Box 7, Folder 98)
      - David Mates to Julius Emspak Regarding Finances, April 28, 1955; 1.
  - Local 726
    - Local 726 Incoming Correspondence, April 21-December 10, 1937 (Box 7, Folder 99)
      - Julius Emspak to Philip Sheridan Regarding Organization, April 21, 1937; 1.
      - Emspak to Sheridan Regarding Organization, May 22, 1937; 2.
      - Emspak to Sheridan Regarding People's Press, July 1, 1937; 3.
      - Emspak to Sam Albaum Regarding Per Capita, December 1, 1937; 4.
      - Unsigned Letter to Albaum Regarding Organization, December 10, 1937; 5.
    - Local 726 Outgoing Correspondence, April 15-December 15, 1937 (Box 7, Folder 100)
      - Sam Albaum to Julius Emspak Regarding Finances, October 25, 1937; 1.
      - Albaum to Emspak Regarding Per Capita, November 24, 1937; 2.
      - Albaum to Emspak Regarding Per Capita and Organization, December 5, 1937; 3.
      - Allan Howey to Emspak Regarding Officers, November 13, 1937; 4.
      - Howey Telegram to James Carey Regarding Labor Unity and Wages, November 20, 1937; 5.
      - Howey to Albert Stonkus Regarding Staff Members, December 15, 1937; 6.
      - Philip Sheridon to Emspak Regarding Organization, April 15, 1937; 7.
      - Sheridon to Emspak Regarding Organization and Staff Members, May 8, 1937; 8.
      - Sheridon to Emspak Regarding Organization, June 8, 1937; 9.
      - Sheridon to Emspak Regarding Membership and Per Capita, July 17, 1937; 10.
      - Sheridon to Emspak Regarding Staff Members, August 1, 1937; 11.
    - Local 726 Financial Secretary Report, July-December 1937 (Box 7, Folder 101)
    - Local 726 Notices of Delinquency and Suspension, November 1937 (Box 7, Folder 102)
    - Local 726 Organization, April 1-12, 1937 (Box 7, Folder 103)
      - Philip Sheridon to John Brophy, April 1, 1937; 1.
      - Brophy to Sheridan, April 12, 1937; 2.
  - Local 728
    - Local 728 Outgoing Correspondence, October 8, 1937-February 18, 1938 (Box 7, Folder 104)
      - Charles Banner to Julius Emspak Regarding Per Capita, October 8, 1937-February 18, 1938; 1-3.
    - Local 728 Financial Secretary Report, June 1937-January 1938 (Box 7, Folder 105)
    - Local 728 Notices of Delinquency and Suspension, November 1937 (Box 7, Folder 106)
    - Local 728 Correspondence, May 24, 1937 (Box 7, Folder 107)
      - James Pascoe to Julius Emspak, May 24, 1937; 1.
  - Local 733
    - Local 733 Officers Lists, October 6, 1937 (Box 7, Folder 108)
    - Local 733 Incoming Correspondence, July 12, 1937 (Box 7, Folder 109)
      - Julius Emspak to Emil Borchardt Regarding Organization, July 12, 1937; 1.
    - Local 733 Outgoing Correspondence, November 1937-May 1938 (Box 7, Folder 110)
      - Monroe Causley to Julius Emspak Regarding Per Capita, November 1937; 1.
      - F. J. Verellen to Emspak Regarding Disbanding, May 8, 1938; 2.
    - Local 733 Notice of Delinquency, December 1937 (Box 7, Folder 111)
    - Local 733 Charter Application, June 24, 1937 (Box 7, Folder 112)
  - Local 736
    - Local 736 Incoming Correspondence, November 8, 1937-January 17, 1938 (Box 7, Folder 113)
      - James Carey to D. E. Hackett Regarding White Collar Organization, November 8, 1937; 1.
      - Julius Emspak to Joseph Ivansco Regarding Dues, December 23, 1937; 2.
      - Emspak to Ivansco Regarding Factionalism and Per Capita, December 29, 1937; 3.
      - Albert Stonkus to Hackett Regarding Utilities Workers Conference and Per Capita, January 17, 1938; 4.
    - Local 736 Outgoing Correspondence, November 3, 1937-January 12, 1938 (Box 7, Folder 114)
      - D. E. Hackett to James Carey Regarding White Collar Organization, November 3, 1937; 1.
      - Hackett to Albert Stonkus Regarding Factionalism and Utility Workers Conference, January 12, 1938; 2.
      - Joseph Ivansco to Julius Emspak Regarding Dues and Negotiations, December 17, 1937; 3.
      - Ivansco to Emspak Regarding Per Capita and Factionalism, December 17, 1937; 4.
    - Local 736 Per Capita Report, July 1937-January 1938 (Box 7, Folder 115)
    - Local 736 Notices of Delinquency and Suspension, November 1937 (Box 7, Folder 116)
    - Local 736 Factionalism, January 4-22, 1938 (Box 7, Folder 117)
      - Charles Killinger to Julius Emspak, January 4, 1938; 1.
      - Emspak to Killinger, January 7, 1938; 2.
      - James Carey to Killinger, January 22, 1938; 3.
    - Local 736 Charter Application, March 23, 1937 (Box 7, Folder 118)
  - Local 737
    - Local 737 Constitution, April 16, 1941 (Box 7, Folder 119)
    - Local 737 Officers Lists, September 8, 1937-December 23, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 120)
    - Local 737 Incoming James Neuman Correspondence, April 17, 1939-July 17, 1941 (Box 7, Folder 121)
      - James Carey Regarding Closed Shop and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Inter-union Rivalry, April 17, 1939; 1.
      - Carey Regarding Constitution, May 3, 1939; 2.
      - Julius Emspak Regarding Organization, July 27, 1937; 3.
      - Emspak Regarding Per Capita, August 11, 1937; 4.
      - Emspak Regarding Organization, September 30, 1937; 5.
      - Emspak Regarding Staff Members, October 1, 1937; 6.
      - Emspak Regarding Finances, December 3, 1937; 7.
      - Emspak Regarding Federation of Architects, Engineers, Chemists and Technicians, December 30, 1937; 8.
      - Emspak Regarding Finances and Unemployment, January 15, 1938; 9.
      - Emspak Regarding 1938 UE Convention, August 20, 1938; 10-11.
      - Emspak Regarding Unemployment, December 28, 1938; 12.
      - Emspak Regarding Contracts and Constitutions, May 11, 1939; 13.
      - Emspak Regarding Essex Wire, May 18, 1939; 14.
      - Emspak Regarding Wages, May 24, 1939; 15.
      - Emspak Regarding Per Capita, May 10, 1940; 16.
      - Emspak Regarding Seniority, June 11, 1940; 17.
      - Emspak Regarding Union Label, August 14, 1940; 18.
      - Emspak Regarding Wages and General Electric Service, May 7, 1941; 19.
      - Emspak Telegram to Arbitration, July 10, 1941; 20.
      - Emspak Regarding Wages, July 17, 1941; 21.
    - Local 737 Incoming James Neuman Correspondence, July 23, 1938-January 7, 1942 (Box 7, Folder 122)
      - Julius Emspak Regarding Wurlitzer Organization, August 1, 1941; 1.
      - Emspak Regarding Union Labels, August 12, 1941; 2.
      - Emspak Regarding Industrial Communications, August 15, 1941; 3.
      - Emspak Regarding District 9, September 19, 1941; 4.
      - Emspak Regarding Industrial Communications, September 22, 1941; 5.
      - Emspak Telegram Regarding Factionalism and Officers, December 4, 1941; 6.
      - Emspak Regarding Factionalism, March 12, 1942; 7.
      - Emspak Regarding Factionalism and Newuman Appeal, April 2, 1942; 18.
      - Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Factionalism and Neuman Appeal, December 31, 1941-January 7, 1942; 9-10.
      - John Lewis Regarding 1938 UE Convention, July 23, 1938; 11.
    - Local 737 Incoming James Neuman Correspondence, October 22, 1937-January 18, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 123)
      - James Matles Regarding Boycotts, November 30, 1938; 1.
      - Matles Regarding Square D Organization, March 24, 1939; 2.
      - Matles Regarding General Electric Service, October 17, 1939; 3.
      - Matles Regarding General Electric Service Contracts, October 31, 1939; 4.
      - Matles Regarding Detroit Visit, May 2, 1941; 5.
      - Matles Regarding United Motors Service Negotiations, June 6, 1941; 6.
      - Matles Regarding Staff Members and Factionalism, July 30, 1941; 7.
      - Matles Regarding American Flourescent, August 12, 1941; 8.
      - Matles Regarding Finances and Staff Members, August 12, 1941; 9.
      - Matles Regarding Teamsters and Staff Members, September 30, 1941; 10.
      - Matles Regarding United Motors Contracts and General Electric Negotiations, October 3, 1941; 11.
      - William Mitchell Regarding Wages and Wire Industry, October 22, 1937; 12.
      - Engineer Regarding Detroit Service Shop Negotiations with Discussion Points and Regulations, January 18, 1940; 13.
    - Local 737 Outgoing James Neuman Correspondence, August 5, 1937-December 28, 1938 (Box 7, Folder 124)
      - James Neuman to Julius Emspak Regarding Organization, Per Capita and 1937 UE Convention, August 5, 1937; 1.
      - Neuman to Emspak Regarding Per Capita, August 12, 1937; 2.
      - Neuman to Emspak Regarding Officers, Essex Wire and United Auto Workers Inter-union Rivalry, September 7, 1937; 3.
      - Neuman to Emspak Regarding UE Constitutions and Staff Members, September 30, 1937; 4.
      - Neuman to Emspak Regarding Supplies with Dues Cards, November 22, 1937; 5.
      - Neuman to James Matles Regarding Dictaphone and Essex Wire, November 23, 1937; 6.
      - Neuman to James Carey Regarding International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Inter-union Rivalry and Minimum Wage, July 8, 1938; 7.
      - Neuman to People's Press Regarding Essex Wire Negotiations, July 19, 1938; 8.
      - Neuman to Emspak Regarding International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Inter-union Rivalry, July 25, 1938; 9.
      - Neuman to Emspak Regarding 1938 UE Convention, August 19, 1938; 10.
      - Neuman to Emspak Regarding Unemployment and Dues, December 15, 1938; 11.
      - Neuman to Matles Regarding Political Action, December 28, 1938; 12.
    - Local 737 Outgoing James Neuman Correspondence, January 6-May 22, 1939 (Box 7, Folder 125)
      - James Neuman to James Matles Regarding Negotiations, January 6, 1939; 1.
      - Neuman to Matles Regarding Essex Wire Wages and United Auto Workers with Wage List, January 24, 19339; 2.
      - Neuman to Matles Regarding Square D Negotiations with Essex Wire Minutes, March 23, 1939; 3.
      - Neuman to Julius Emspak Regarding Factionalism and Essex Wire Charters, April 6-12, 1939; 4-5.
      - Neuman to James Carey Regarding International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Inter-union Rivalry and Square D Negotiations with February 1939, C. F. Finny Report, Febrary 1939, M. W. McKinnon Report, April 7, 1939, Bates Letter and April 10, 1939, Warton Summary, April 13, 1939; 6.
      - Neuman to Carey Regarding International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Inter-union Rivalry, Factionalism and Essex Wire Seperate Charter, April 24, 1939; 7.
      - Neuman to Emspak Regarding Square D Contracts and United Auto Workers, May 1, 1939; 8.
      - Neuman to Emspak Regarding Factionalism and Essex Wire Seperate Charter, May 13, 1939; 9.
      - Neuman to Emspak Regarding American Heater Negotiations, May 22, 1939; 10.
    - Local 737 Outgoing James Neuman Correspondence, October 10, 1939-April 26, 1940 (Box 8, Folder 1)
      - James Neuman to James Matles Regarding Finances and General Electric Service with General Electric Service Proposed Agreement, October 10, 1939; 1.
      - Neuman to Matles Regarding General Electric Services and Essex Wire Inter-union Rivalry, October 16, 1939; 2.
      - Neuman to Matles Regarding General Electric Service Negotiations and Carbolog, November 13, 1939; 3.
      - Neuman to Matles Regarding General Electric Service Negotiations and Carbalog with November 27, 1939 Statements from Priscilla Dodd, Daniel Burns and Arthur Barker, November 29, 1939; 4.
      - Neuman to Matles Regarding General Electric Service Negotiations and Carbalog, November 24, 1939; 5.
      - Neuman Telegram to Julius Emspak Regarding Carbalog, December 5, 1939; 6.
      - Neuman to Matles Regarding American Heater Wages, December 8, 1939; 7.
      - Neuman to Matles Regarding General Electric Services and Factionalism, January 4, 1940; 8.
      - Neuman to Matles Regarding General Electric Service Negotiations and Carbaloy, January 5, 1940; 9.
      - Neuman to Matles Regarding General Electric Service Negotiations, Factionalism and Greenville, January 11, 1940; 10.
      - Neuman to Emspak Regarding Per Capita and Unemployment, April 26, 1940; 11.
    - Local 737 Outgoing James Neuman Correspondence, May 9, 1940-September 23, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 2)
      - James Neuman to James Matles Regarding Jukebox Contracts, May 9, 1940; 1.
      - Neuman to Julius Emspak Regarding General Electric Service Seniority, May 31, 1940; 2.
      - Neuman to Emspak Regarding General Electric Service, June 24, 1940; 3.
      - Neuman to James Carey Regarding Legislation, November 15, 1940; 4.
      - Neuman to Emspak Regarding American Heater Negotiations and Firings, January 15, 1941; 5.
      - Neuman to Matles Regarding Detroit Visit, April 10, 1941; 6.
      - Neuman to Emspak Regarding Union Label, April 10, 1941; 7.
      - Neuman to Matles Regarding Detroit Visit, April 29, 1941; 8.
      - Neuman to Emspak Regarding General Motors Service Negotiations, June 5, 1941; 9.
      - Neuman to Matles Regarding Detroit and Factionalism, July 3, 1941; 10.
      - Neuman to Matles Regarding Square D Negotiations, July 3, 1941; 11.
      - Neuman to Emspak Regarding Wagner Electric Contracts and General Motors Service with Notice of Election, July 21, 1941; 12.
      - Neuman to Emspak Regarding Pine Organs, July 23, 1941; 13.
      - Neuman to Matles Regarding Bull Dog Electric, United Motors and Detroit, August 7, 1941; 14.
      - Neuman to Matles Regarding Industrial Communication Contracts, August 13, 1941; 15.
      - Neuman to Matles Regarding Radio Service and American Federation of Labor Inter-union Rivalry with July 29, 1941, August Scholle Letter to F. F. Spencer and July 26, 1941, Spencer Letter to Scholle, August 18, 1941; 16.
      - Neuman to Emspak Regarding District 9, September 15, 1941; 17.
      - Neuman to Matles Regarding Detroit and Inter-union Rivalry, September 19, 1941; 18.
      - Neuman to Emspak Regarding Industrial Communications, September 23, 1941; 19.
    - Local 737 Outgoing James Neuman Correspondence, October 1, 1941-March 17, 1942 (Box 8, Folder 3)
      - James Neuman to Julius Emspak Regarding Metro Auto Electric and Miller-Seldon Contracts, October 1, 1941; 1.
      - Neuman to Emspak Regarding United Motors Service Contracts, October 2, 1941; 2.
      - Neuman Telegram to Albert Fitgerald Regarding Factionalism and Officers, December 5, 1941; 3.
      - Neuman to Fitzgerald Regarding Factionalism with December 14, 1941, Resolution, December 20, 1941; 4.
      - Neuman to Fitzgerald Regarding Factionalism and Officers, December 24, 1941; 5.
      - Neuman to Julius Emspak Regarding Union Label, December 31, 1941; 6.
      - Neuman to Emspak Regarding Factionalism, January 2, 1942; 7.
      - Neuman Telegram to Fitzgerald Regarding Factionalism and Officers, January 2, 1942; 8.
      - Neuman to Emspak Regarding Factionalism and Officers, March 17, 1942; 9.
    - Local 737 Incoming Correspondence, January 26-June 16, 1942 (Box 8, Folder 4)
      - Carl Bersing to Local 737 Regarding Electric Storage Battery Negotiations, January 26, 1942; 1.
      - Julius Emspak to R. A. Morris Regarding 1938 UE Convention, June 23, 1938; 2.
      - Emspak to Rusell Beaubien Regarding Factionalism, April 12, 1939; 3.
      - Emspak to Morris Regarding Seperate Charter, May 11, 1939; 4.
      - Emspak to Erich Schmidt Regarding Finances and Per Capita, April 2, 1940; 5.
      - Emspak to Carl Goeltz Regarding General Electric Service and Fringe Benefits, April 26, 1940; 6.
      - Emspak to R. Sieger Regarding Seniority, May 16, 1940; 7.
      - Emspak to Schmidt Regarding American Heater Strikes, April 1-9, 1941; 8-9.
      - Emspak to Schmidt Regarding Strikes, April 15, 1941; 10.
      - Emspak to Schmidt Regarding American Heater Strikes, April 28, 1941; 11.
      - Emspak to Albert Stakses, October 27, 1941; 12.
      - Emspak to Hawey Harrington Regarding Per Capita, December 16, 1941; 13.
      - Emspak to Harry Evans Regarding Lost Time, February 13, 1942; 14.
      - Emspak to Lillian Czaja Regarding Transfers, July 20, 1942; 15.
      - Emspak to Charles Richmon Regarding American Federation of Labor Inter-union Rivalry, November 4, 1942; 16.
      - Albert Fitzgerald to Evans Regarding American Federation of Labor Inter-union Rivalry, June 16, 1942; 17.
    - Local 737 Incoming Correspondence, May 31, 1938-October 22, 1942 (Box 8, Folder 5)
      - James Matles to R. A. Morris Regarding Local 1116 Strikes, May 31, 1938; 1.
      - Matles to Harvey Harrington Regarding American Heater Strikes, May 16, 1941; 2.
      - Matles to Harry Evans Regarding General Motors Corporation, February 19-March 23, 1942; 3-4.
      - Matles to Charles Richmond Regarding Detrola, September 24, 1942; 5.
      - Matles to Richmond Regarding Pioneer Pump, October 22, 1942; 6.
      - Matles to Richmond Regarding Finances and Negotiations, October 22, 1942; 7.
    - Local 737 Outgoing Correspondence, March 30, 1939-July 14, 1942 (Box 8, Folder 6)
      - Russell Beaubien to UE Regarding Essex Wire Seperate Charter, April 10, 1939; 1.
      - Lillian Czaja to Julius Emspak Regarding Officers, July 9, 1942; 2.
      - Czaja to Regarding Supplies, July 8, 1942; 3.
      - Czaja to Emspak Regardign General Electric Service Transfers, July 13, 1942; 4.
      - Harry Davis to UE Regarding Essex Wire Seperate Charter, March 30, 1939; 5.
      - Ed Derickson to Emspak Regarding District 9, December 13, 1941; 6.
      - Harry Evans to M. Palmer Regardig Westinghouse Organization, January 29, 1942; 7.
      - Evans to James Matles Regarding Westinghouse Conference Board, February 3, 1942; 8.
      - Evans to Matles Regarding General Motors Grievances and Negotiations, February 3, 1942; 9.
      - Evans to Emspak Regarding General Electric Service and Grievances, February 6, 1942; 10.
      - Evans to Matles Regarding Negotiations and American Heater Strikes, March 19, 1942; 11.
      - Evans to Michigan State Mediation Board Regarding Square D Negotiations, April 2, 1942; 12.
      - Evans to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding American Federation of Labor Inter-union Rivalry with Memo, June 1, 1942; 13.
      - Evans Telegram to Emspak Regarding Factionalism and Officers, 14.
      - Evans Telegram to Matles Regarding Factionalism and Officers, 15.
      - Evans Telegram to Emspak Regarding Factionalism and Officers, 16.
      - C. E. Goeltz to Emspak Regarding Officers, January 3, 1941; 17.
      - Rita Hodyka to Matles Regarding Staff Members, Factionalism and Detrola Strikes, June 17, 1942; 18.
      - Edwin Insho to Charles Newell Regarding Westinghouse Service Negotiations, June 9, 1942; 19.
    - Local 737 Outgoing Correspondence, May 2, 1939-January 14, 1943 (Box 8, Folder 7)
      - Bert Morris to James Matles Regarding General Electric Service Negotiations, July 13, 1942; 1.
      - Morris to UE Regarding Officers, January 14, 1943; 2.
      - R. A. Morris to Julius Emspak Regarding Essex Wire Seperate Charter, May 2, 1939; 3.
      - Pauline Diphant to Matles Regarding Westinghouse Conference Board, October 13, 1941; 4.
      - Diphant to Matles Regarding Westinghouse Conference Board, January 9, 1942; 5.
      - Charles Richmond Telegram to Matles Regarding Contracts, July 28, 1942; 6.
      - Richmond to Matles Regarding Staff Members, August 5, 1942; 7.
      - Richmond Telegram to Matles Regarding Westinghouse and Wages, August 6, 1942; 8.
      - Richmond to John Steelman Regarding Westinghouse Contracts, August 13, 1942; 9.
      - Richmond to Sam McAfee Regarding Finances, August 19, 1942; 10.
      - Richmond to Matles Regarding Finances, August 27, 1942; 11.
      - Richmond to Matles Regarding Staff Members, August 31, 1942; 12.
      - Richmond to Emspak Regarding American Federation of Labor Inter-union Rivalry, September 21, 1942; 13.
      - Richmond to Matles Regarding Finances, General Electric Negotiations and Westinghouse with Local Minutes, October 8, 1942; 14.
      - Richmond to Emspak Regarding American Federation of Labor Inter-union Rivalry, November 2, 1942; 15.
      - Richmond to Matles Regarding Pioneer Negotiations, November 6, 1942; 16.
      - Richmond to Matles Regarding Decca Membership and Wages, November 25, 1942; 17.
      - Richmond to Matles Regarding Decca Negotiations, December 23, 1942; 18.
      - Richmond to Matles Regarding General Electric Service Negotiations, December 30, 1942; 19.
      - Richmond to Matles Regarding Decca Membership, Negotiations and Wages, January 12, 1943; 20.
      - Richmond to Matles Regarding Pioneer Pump Contracts and War Labor Board, January 13, 1943; 21.
    - Local 737 Outgoing Correspondence, March 25, 1940-January 19, 1942 (Box 8, Folder 8)